<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sean Connelly</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sean Connelly</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Voters&#39; Windshield Perspective</title>
      <link>/2018/07/04/census-mapping-rmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/07/04/census-mapping-rmd/</guid>
      <description>Happy Fourth of July! Given the holiday, I thought it would be fitting to look at the intersection of politics and transportation. Last week, Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, a 28-year-old democratic socialist, defeated Joe Crowley, the incumbent who was tapped as the next Democratic House Speaker, in the New York 14th Congressional District (NY-14) primary. Ocasio-Cortez’s victory made national news, which is no surprise given the natural story lines (grassroots versus establishment, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PBLs and Sunshine</title>
      <link>/2018/06/02/pbl-networks-rmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/02/pbl-networks-rmd/</guid>
      <description>It’s finally summertime here in New York, which means bike season is upon us. Since the turn of the millennium, cycling as a mode of transportation has exploded in the US; the Census Bureau recorded a 60 percent increase in bike commuting between 2000 and 2012. This increase in participation has gone hand in hand with the expansion of biking facilities and infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First GitHub Pages Post!</title>
      <link>/2018/05/04/first-post-rmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/04/first-post-rmd/</guid>
      <description>New HomeHi there - how do you like the new digs? After a brief hiatus during grad school application season, I found myself ready to dive back into data, but extremely frustrated with GitHub documents as a medium to share my work. Enter blogdown and GitHub Pages! The blogdown R package makes it easy to create a website using nothing but R Markdown, and then host it on your free personal GitHub URL.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>